module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'He died _____ a severe head injury.',
    choices: ['on', 'of', 'from', 'with'],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'The cat entered _____ the room through the window.',
    choices: ['in', 'into', 'out', 'no preposition'],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'India and America entered _____ a nuclear agreement',
    choices: ['Into', 'in', 'with', 'by'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    question: 'You are liable _____ the damage of the properties',
    choices: ['with', 'to', 'with', 'for'],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'You are liable _____ pay the income tax.',
    choices: ['for', 'to', 'in', 'in'],
    correctAnswer: 4
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the goal of providing constructive feedback in the workplace?',
    choices: [
      'Let employees know the manager is aware of their negative behaviors.',
      'Build good rapport with employees by providing regular praise.',
      'Communicating in public to promote a sense of transparency about issues.',
      'Criticize personal traits that can be worked on by the employee.'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question:
      "Bubba listened to Sunny explain that the customers who had issues with her table requests were there during the busiest time periods. Because of this, she was unable to service all of her tables' requests in time. This is an example of which constructive feedback guideline?",
    choices: [
      'Let the recipient of the feedback respond.',
      'Criticize only behavior and not personal traits.',
      'Ask questions to obtain more clarity.',
      'Conduct a self-assessment before the review.'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a suggestion for giving constructive feedback?',
    choices: [
      'Choose an appropriate setting to deliver feedback.',
      'Give a positive feedback sandwich.',
      'Criticize only behavior and not personal traits.',
      'Provide direct, honest and specific feedback.'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'In which of the following situations would Mick, a supervisor, need to address the area of self-regulation with Cas, his employee?',
    choices: [
      "Cas doesn't know how to approach other people in social situations",
      'Cas never takes time off and seems to work constantly',
      'Cas is prone to outbursts and mood swings',
      "Cas doesn't really seem to care about other people"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following represents two broad categories of interpersonal interactions?',
    choices: ['Vocal and spontaneous', 'Verbal and non-verbal', 'Excited and anticipatory', 'Non-verbal and conflicting'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }
]
